Because you are my brother.
당신은 내 형제이기 때문입니다.
Xiao Douzi knocked you out
Xiao Douzi가 당신을 쓰러뜨렸습니다
of course he should apologize to you.
물론 그는 당신에게 사과해야 합니다.
However, you also feel uncomfortable riding it again.
그러나 다시 타면 불편함을 느끼기도 합니다.
You should apologize to him too.
당신도 그 사람에게 사과해야 해요.
This problem started with me.
이 문제는 나에게서 시작되었습니다.
I also keep Xiao Douzi.
나는 또한 Xiao Douzi를 유지합니다.
So I also have to apologize to both of you
그러니까 나도 두 사람한테 사과해야지
you're not normal
당신은 정상이 아니다
if it's still not normal
그래도 정상이 아니라면
I'll chase him away for you.
내가 당신을 위해 그 사람을 쫓아내겠습니다.
I won't take you
난 당신을 데려가지 않을 거예요
believe it or not?
믿거 나 말거나?
Sis.
언니.
Sister-in-law.
시누이.
Charm.
매력.
Why is it here?
왜 여기에 있나요?
I understand.
이해합니다.
Sis,
언니,
You and Mrs. Luo want to continue their relationship again.
당신과 Luo 부인은 그들의 관계를 다시 계속하고 싶어합니다.
Mei Kai dua kali
메이 카이 두아 칼리
humble.
겸손한.
This time can't let Guan Qun know anymore.
이번에는 더 이상 Guan Qun에게 알릴 수 없습니다.
Truly.
진심으로.
Indeed, we met the forest after a long dry season.
실제로 우리는 긴 건기를 지나 숲을 만났습니다.
Otherwise, why did her earring break too?
그렇지 않으면 왜 그녀의 귀걸이도 부러졌을까요?
You go. Go.
너가. 가다.
You just go busy.
당신은 바쁘다.
Sister.
자매.
Quickly return your earrings.
귀걸이를 빨리 돌려주세요.
So as not to be discovered by Luo Guanqun again.
다시는 Luo Guanqun에게 발견되지 않도록.
First of all I want to know
우선 알고 싶습니다.
your specific action plan is still a plan
귀하의 구체적인 행동 계획은 여전히 ​​​​계획입니다
we will move with the storm team
우리는 폭풍 팀과 함께 움직일 것이다
save the kidnapped members first
납치된 멤버들을 먼저 구해주세요
and also the workers
그리고 노동자들도
then set the bomb
그럼 폭탄을 설치해
destroy the counterfeit money factory.
위조지폐 공장을 파괴하라.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Our plan is problematic.
우리 계획에 문제가 있습니다.
I've asked.
나는 물었다.
This factory continues production 24 hours,
이 공장은 24시간 생산을 계속하고 있으며,
at the same time, it still exists
동시에 그것은 여전히 ​​존재한다
teams of Japanese soldiers stood guard day and night.
일본군 부대가 밤낮으로 경비를 서고 있었습니다.
Want to enter from the main door
정문으로 들어가고 싶어요
that's very difficult.
그것은 매우 어렵습니다.
So, you underestimated Team Storm's combat power.
그래서 당신은 팀 스톰의 전투력을 과소평가했군요.
Enough to face some unprepared Japanese troops.
준비되지 않은 일본군을 상대하기에 충분합니다.
Still many.
아직도 많습니다.
But don't forget,
하지만 잊지 마세요.
Shanghai-Xi section of the Military Police Headquarters
헌병사령부 상하이시과
is 15 minutes from this factory
이 공장에서 15분 거리에 있어요
from this factory.
이 공장에서.
Once the battle begins,
전투가 시작되면,
their help will be very fast.
그들의 도움은 매우 빠를 것입니다.
If so, what is your suggestion?
그렇다면, 당신의 제안은 무엇입니까?
There is only one way
방법은 오직 하나뿐이다
say it.
말해.
Every 8 p.m
오후 8시마다
office workers in this factory
이 공장의 직장인들
and also night shift workers.
그리고 야간 교대근무자들도요.
Will change shifts.
교대근무를 변경합니다.
Apart from the workers
노동자들 외에도
Japanese troops
일본군
will be guarded by two soldiers,
두 명의 군인이 지키고,
others will also change shifts.
다른 사람들도 교대 근무를 바꿀 것입니다.
So in this time
그래서 이 시간에
in the entire factory there were only two foremen
공장 전체에는 감독관이 두 명뿐이었습니다.
there are still 2 Japanese soldiers
아직 일본군이 2명 남아있습니다
is when the defense is very weak.
수비가 너무 약할 때다.
Correct.
옳은.
But this shift change won't take too long.
그러나 이러한 교대 근무 변경은 그리 오래 걸리지 않을 것입니다.
20 minutes at most.
최대 20분.
Twenty minutes.
20분.
In that case, we simply don't have time to deploy
그렇다면 배포할 시간이 없습니다.
and perform operations.
그리고 작업을 수행합니다.
However, if within these 20 minutes
그러나 이 20분 이내에
can reach the target,
목표에 도달할 수 있고,
I think we still have a chance of success.
아직은 성공할 가능성이 있다고 생각해요.
You mean the right target?
타겟이 맞다는 뜻인가요?
Before the operation begins
수술이 시작되기 전에
we go into the factory,
우리는 공장에 들어가고,
Look for the location of the money printing factory.
화폐 인쇄 공장의 위치를 ​​찾아보세요.
Then, ask the Storm Team to get straight to the point.
그런 다음 폭풍 팀에 바로 요점을 알려달라고 요청하세요.
Before help arrives,
도움이 도착하기 전에,
we completed the mission.
우리는 임무를 완료했습니다.
This factory
이 공장
continuously producing for 24 hours
24시간 연속 생산
Apart from that, there is a team of Japanese soldiers
그 외에도 일본군 팀이 있습니다
how do we get in
우리는 어떻게 들어가나요?
So,
그래서,
You know I'm the one who takes care of general affairs,
내가 총무를 담당하는 거 알잖아.
Let's just say your luck is good.
운이 좋다고만 말해두자.
I've asked.
나는 물었다.
Lunch and dinner at this factory.
이 공장에서 점심과 저녁을 먹습니다.
By a restaurant in town
동네 식당에서
the so-called restaurant opening restaurant.
소위 레스토랑 오픈 레스토랑.
Wait until the dining cart arrives at the factory
식당 카트가 공장에 도착할 때까지 기다리십시오
the foreman will check all workers' certificates
감독은 모든 근로자의 증명서를 확인합니다
then a restaurant worker
그럼 식당 직원
bringing food into the factory,
공장으로 식품을 가져오고,
one by one.
하나씩.
What you mean is
당신이 의미하는 바는
we can disguise ourselves as restaurant employees.
식당 직원으로 변장할 수 있어요.
Correct
옳은
the scale of this restaurant is large
이 식당의 규모는 크다
there are lots of people
사람이 많아요
its mobility is frequently used.
이동성이 자주 사용됩니다.
The foreman cannot possibly know everyone's face.
감독은 모든 사람의 얼굴을 알 수 없습니다.
As long as we make witnesses as one,...
우리가 하나로 증인이 되는 한...
Then the foreman will no longer be suspicious.
그러면 감독은 더 이상 의심하지 않을 것입니다.
But even if we enter the factory,
하지만 공장에 들어가도
how can you find a counterfeit money factory?
위조지폐 공장은 어떻게 찾을 수 있나요?
I'm considering it too.
저도 고려 중이에요.
We now have absolutely no clue.
이제 우리는 전혀 단서가 없습니다.
Guoguo,
궈궈,
try to think about it.
그것에 대해 생각해보십시오.
The Japanese locked up workers and experts.
일본인은 노동자와 전문가를 가두었습니다.
But it must ensure their basic survival every day
하지만 매일 기본적인 생존을 보장해야 합니다.
right, right?
맞아 맞아?
Good.
좋은.
The counterfeit money factory numbers 30 to 40 people.
위조지폐공장의 인원은 30~40명이다.
Plus Japanese troops
게다가 일본군
how to prepare their food?
음식을 어떻게 준비하나요?
I remember Guo Yun once said,
Guo Yun이 다음과 같이 말한 것을 기억합니다.
they can eat buns every afternoon.
그들은 매일 오후에 빵을 먹을 수 있어요.
My wife's memory is the best.
아내의 기억력은 최고입니다.
Correct.
옳은.
Lunch, eat two packs of vegetables,
점심은 야채 2팩을 먹고,
the night of porridge and flower rolls.
죽과 꽃말이의 밤.
Once every week
매주 한 번씩
= Gemice = You can eat meat buns once at night
= Gemice = 고기빵은 밤에 한 번 먹을 수 있습니다
This is the opening restaurant menu.
오픈식당 메뉴판입니다.
I understand.
이해합니다.
The food they send to the military clothing factory,
군복공장에 보내는 식량,
actually there are some,
사실 그런 분들도 계시고,
sent to an underground counterfeit money factory
지하 위조지폐 공장으로 보내짐
Correct.
옳은.
There must be someone
누군가가 있을 거에요
send some of the food to a counterfeit money factory.
음식 일부를 위조지폐 공장으로 보내세요.
As long as we follow this guy,
이 사람을 따라가는 한,
we can find out the location of this counterfeit money factory.
이 위조지폐 공장의 위치를 ​​알아낼 수 있어요.
This is a great way.
이것은 좋은 방법입니다.
Go down.
내려가세요.
Give me the ring.
반지를 주세요.
Remember that.
기억.
Do not speak.
말하지 않는다.
After this operation is complete,
이 작업이 완료된 후,
commander of the Military Police Soldiers
헌병대 사령관
will definitely do research on all of us.
확실히 우리 모두에 대해 조사를 할 것입니다.
Including everyone in the factory.
공장의 모든 사람을 포함합니다.
Will check one by one.
하나씩 확인해보겠습니다.
We are some people disguised as delivery people
우리는 배달원으로 변장한 사람들이에요
the picture will definitely be painted.
그림은 반드시 그려질 것이다.
Especially the two of us,
특히 우리 둘은
frequent contact with Japanese people.
일본인과 자주 접촉한다.
So you have to pretend well
그러니 잘하는 척 해야 해
I saw today they eat meatloaf.
오늘 보니 미트 로프를 먹는군요.
These two big buckets were supposed to be for workers
이 두 개의 큰 양동이는 작업자를 위한 것이었습니다.
the two below,
아래 두 개,
should have been sent to a counterfeit money factory.
위조지폐 공장으로 보냈어야 했는데.
Your analysis is not wrong.
당신의 분석은 틀리지 않았습니다.
In this basket,
이 바구니에는
supposedly for Japanese soldiers and foremen.
아마도 일본 군인과 감독을위한 것입니다.
How do we divide the tasks later?
나중에 작업을 어떻게 나누나요?
You guys distribute buns to the workers outside.
밖에 있는 일꾼들에게 빵을 나눠주네요.
I went to serve the Japanese and the foreman.
나는 일본인과 감독에게 봉사하러 갔다.
I'm coming with you.
나는 당신과 함께 갈 것입니다.
Don't believe me.
내 말을 믿지 마세요.
Good.
좋은.
No problem.
괜찮아요.
Guoguo, help me look for a moment.
Guoguo, 잠시만 찾도록 도와주세요.
Why is it so late today?
오늘은 왜 이렇게 늦었나요?
Why have you just arrived?
왜 방금 도착했어요?
Far
멀리
Why is everyone foreign today?
오늘은 왜 다 외국인이에요?
Change people again.
사람을 다시 바꾸세요.
You go ask the boss.
가서 사장님한테 물어보세요.
I see your emotions are not small.
나는 당신의 감정이 작지 않다는 것을 봅니다.
Of course.
물론.
Sending 50 minutes to you
당신에게 보내는 50분
delivery to the city only a dozen minutes,
시내까지 단 12분만에 배송,
give me the same salary.
나에게도 같은 급여를 줘.
If you don't have emotions,
감정이 없다면,
Have you brought your ID?
신분증을 가져오셨나요?
Stop it.
그만해요.
Here.
여기.
Help me.
도와주세요.
Work quickly.
빨리 일하세요.
When we're finished, we'll go home quickly
끝나면 우리 빨리 집에 갈게요
quickly dry or dissolve
빠르게 건조되거나 용해됨
your face comes out
얼굴이 나오네
have you finished looking?
다 찾아봤어?
Wait.
기다리다.
If you don't want to come,
오기 싫으면,
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
It's me.
나야.
At that time fighting with guests,
그 당시 손님과 싸우던 중,
made Boss Zhou angry.
Zhou 상사를 화나게 만들었습니다.
Because I,
왜냐면 난,
because I.
왜냐면 난.
How is Boss Zhou?
주 사장은 어떤가요?
I'm asking you.
나는 당신에게 묻고 있습니다.
Mute.
무음.
Can not hear?
들을수 없어?
Boss Zhou recently married his second wife.
Zhou 사장은 최근 두 번째 아내와 결혼했습니다.
He married a second wife
그는 두 번째 부인과 결혼했다
it's all money to exploit us
우리를 착취하는 것은 모두 돈이다
in your opinion second family
당신 생각에는 두 번째 가족
is he also part of us?
그 사람도 우리의 일부인가요?
You're a kid
당신은 어린 아이입니다
It's finished?
끝났나요?
Go with me.
나랑 같이 가자.
Go away.
저리 가요.
Go ahead.
계속하세요.
Come on, come in quickly.
자, 빨리 들어오세요.
Fast.
빠른.
Hello, sir
안녕하세요 선생님
time to eat
먹을 시간
here, here, lined up.
여기, 여기, 줄을 서세요.
Here.
여기.
Here. Fast.
여기. 빠른.
Go there!
저기로가!
Fast!
빠른!
This.
이것.
You guys pick this up
여러분 이거 뽑아보세요
fast.
빠른.
Where is ours?
우리는 어디에 있습니까?
Follow me.
나를 따르라.
Road.
도로.
Kapten Matsumoto.
Kapten Matsumoto.
Dinner has arrived.
저녁 식사가 도착했습니다.
This.
이것.
What are you eating today?
오늘은 뭘 먹나요?
I'm talking to him.
나는 그와 이야기하고 있습니다.
Kapten Matsumoto.
Kapten Matsumoto.
He's mute.
그는 벙어리입니다.
Senior officers don't be angry.
고위 간부들은 화를 내지 않습니다.
That's it.
그게 다야.
Let me introduce you, okay?
소개할게요, 알았죠?
Today's dish is this white cut chicken.
오늘의 요리는 화이트컷 치킨입니다.
Boiled eggplant with oil.
가지를 기름에 삶은 것.
Shrimp fried in oil,
기름에 튀긴 새우,
white grilled salty
흰색으로 구운 짠맛
Iga babi Hu Jiang
이가 바비 후 지앙
and also mustard soup
그리고 머스타드 수프도 있어요
these vegetables are delicious.
이 야채는 맛있어요.
Hurry up.
서둘러요.
Senior officers, eat slowly.
선배님들, 천천히 드세요.
I'll deliver the food first.
음식 먼저 배달할게요.
Stay cool.
침착.
We will go back to the way it was before
우린 다시 예전처럼 돌아갈 거야
we will provide the best food for you.
우리는 당신에게 최고의 음식을 제공할 것입니다.
Sir, very good.
선생님, 아주 좋아요.
Take good care of the chiefs.
족장들을 잘 보살펴주세요.
I accompanied him to deliver vegetables.
나는 그와 함께 야채를 배달했습니다.
No need, I'll go alone.
필요없어요, 나 혼자 갈게요.
Stupid!
멍청한!
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
No points?
포인트가 없나요?
Be careful.
조심하세요.
Is the King okay?
왕은 괜찮아?
Look at it.
보세요.
Fast.
빠른.
I'm telling you.
나는 당신에게 말하고있다.
Give me eyes.
나에게 눈을 줘.
Hear not?
들리지 않나요?
Pak,
박,
Then I'll go first.
그럼 나 먼저 갈게.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Wait a minute
잠깐 기다려요
shrimp
새우
Good stuff.
좋은 물건.
Shrimp.
새우.
Fall to the floor.
바닥에 떨어지십시오.
You...
너...
Eat it.
그것을 먹을.
Thank you sir
감사합니다
eat it
그것을 먹을
Shrimp is good stuff.
새우는 좋은 물건입니다.
Shrimp must eat.
새우는 꼭 먹어야 합니다.
Shrimp?
새우?
Very delicious.
아주 맛있는.
Thank you, senior officer.
고마워요, 고위 장교님.
Wait!
기다리다!
This side street
이 골목
go quickly!
빨리 가!
Hear not?
들리지 않나요?
I'm afraid I won't be able to catch up.
따라잡지 못할까 두렵습니다.
He did something to the tow truck.
그는 견인 트럭에 뭔가를 했습니다.
Who's that?
저 사람은 누구야?
Go, hurry. We'll get caught.
가, 서둘러. 우리는 잡힐 것이다.
Help me
도와주세요
I beg you.
부탁드립니다.
If we don't leave, we'll be found out.
우리가 떠나지 않으면 우리는 들키게 될 것입니다.
He's seen us.
그 사람이 우리를 본 적이 있어요.
If you don't help him, you will be found out.
그를 돕지 않으면 발각될 것입니다.
Foreman Sun had already gone far away.
선 감독은 이미 멀리 떠났습니다.
Thank you for helping me.
도와 주셔서 감사합니다.
Earlier if I was caught,
예전에 잡혔으면
I will definitely die.
나는 확실히 죽을 것이다.
Now you will die too, understand?
이제 너도 죽을 거야, 알겠니?
Wait.
기다리다.
He works in a uniform factory.
그는 유니폼 공장에서 일한다.
If you don't kill him,
그 사람을 죽이지 않으면,
he's going to leak us!
그 사람이 우리한테 정보를 유출할 거야!
I... I won't tell you guys!
나... 말하지 않겠습니다!
I just want to steal things to fill my stomach.
나는 단지 배를 채우기 위해 물건을 훔치고 싶을 뿐입니다.
I have absolutely no idea what you guys are doing.
나는 너희들이 무엇을 하고 있는지 전혀 모른다.
You wild child!
이 야생 자식!
Ruining our big plans.
우리의 큰 계획을 망치고 있습니다.
No.
아니요.
Wait.
기다리다.
You climb the wall
당신은 벽을 오르다
to steal food to fill the stomach.
배를 채우기 위해 음식을 훔치는 것.
Correct.
옳은.
Our dinner is just a bowl of porridge, a loaf of bread.
우리의 저녁은 단지 죽 한 그릇, 빵 한 덩어리일 뿐입니다.
Not full at all.
전혀 가득 차지 않습니다.
Where do you want to steal it?
어디에서 훔치고 싶나요?
foreman Sun
감독 썬
The stroller has an iron bucket
유모차에는 철제 양동이가 있습니다.
there is bread in it
그 안에 빵이 들어있어요
how do you know?
어떻게 알아?
In foreman Sun's iron bucket are there buns?
선 감독의 쇠통에 빵이 들어있나요?
I stole it once.
한 번 훔쳤어요.
Where
어디
once before
전에 한 번
I work in a barren place
나는 척박한 곳에서 일한다
I saw foreman Sun pushing a trolley
나는 Sun 감독이 트롤리를 밀고 있는 것을 보았습니다.
past there.
거기를 지나서.
I'm thinking
나는 생각 중입니다
what is on the iron barrel?
철통에 뭐가 있지?
is there food in it?
거기에 음식이 들어있나요?
So I followed him
그래서 나는 그를 따라갔다.
up to the warehouse door
창고 문까지
foreman Sun opened the warehouse door and entered
선 감독은 창고 문을 열고 들어갔다.
the stroller stopped there
유모차는 거기에 멈췄다
I took the opportunity to get closer
좀 더 가까이 다가가는 기회를 잡았어요
to open the iron box.
철 상자를 열려면
Inside it turned out to be full of meat buns.
그 안에는 고기 만두가 가득 들어있었습니다.
I took two then ran.
나는 두 개를 가지고 달렸다.
Don't smell it again.
다시는 냄새를 맡지 마세요.
Remember which warehouse?
어느 창고를 기억하시나요?
Still remember.
아직도 기억하다.
Is warehouse number 23
창고번호는 23번인가요?
Do you know the way?
그 길을 아시나요?
Know.
알다.
Take us away.
우리를 데려가세요.
Otherwise, I will kill you!
그렇지 않으면 내가 당신을 죽일 것입니다!
Good.
좋은.
Road.
도로.
What way?
어떤 방법으로?
Over there.
저기요.
Good.
좋은.
Possible.
가능한.
Why did he come back again?
그 사람은 왜 다시 돌아왔나요?
Look at this bucket,
이 양동이를 보세요.
we didn't bring it here, right?
우리가 여기로 가져온 건 아니지, 그렇지?
This means he has finished delivering the food.
이는 그가 음식 배달을 마쳤다는 것을 의미합니다.
What he took was yesterday's bucket
그가 가져간 것은 어제의 양동이였다
street
거리
Road.
도로.
Here.
여기.
This is warehouse number 23.
23번 창고입니다.
When I came,
내가 왔을 때,
here it is guarded by Japanese soldiers.
이곳은 일본군이 지키고 있다.
I took advantage of them going to the toilet.
나는 그들이 화장실에 가는 것을 이용했다.
just got the buns
방금 빵을 샀어
are you sure?
확실합니까?
Confident.
자신감.
Good.
좋은.
Hurry home.
서둘러 집으로 가세요.
It's time to share the food.
음식을 나눠먹는 시간이에요.
I guess.
아마도.
You must be fighting Japan, right?
일본과 싸워야겠죠?
Stop talking nonsense!
말도 안되는 소리는 그만둬!
Still have.
아직 있어요.
Remember, okay?
기억해, 알았지?
Don't tell anyone
아무에게도 말하지 마세요
can't tell anyone else.
다른 사람에게 말할 수 없습니다.
Was it just that I didn't say one word?
내가 한 마디도 안 해서 그런 걸까?
I am also an opponent of Japan.
나 또한 일본의 반대자이다.
You ask him.
당신은 그에게 물어보세요.
Aren't you afraid he'll betray us?
그 사람이 우리를 배신할까 두렵지 않나요?
One day if I'm betrayed,
어느 날 배신당한다면,
then it must not be him.
그렇다면 그 사람이 아니어야 합니다.
The counterfeit money factory is definitely here.
위조지폐 공장은 분명 여기에 있습니다.
But don't you find it strange?
그런데 이상하지 않나요?
This important place
이 중요한 장소
not even the military police were there.
헌병도 거기에 없었습니다.
It's also too quiet.
또한 너무 조용합니다.
I'll go take a look.
나는 가서 살펴볼 것이다.
Now it's time to eat.
이제 먹을 시간입니다.
The Military Police must have delivered buns for them.
헌병대가 그들에게 빵을 배달해 준 게 틀림없다.
Because the buns were sent here,
빵이 여기로 보내졌기 때문에
there's definitely no problem
확실히 문제는 없어
the time is almost here,
시간이 거의 다 왔어.
go quickly
빨리 가세요
Hello, senior officer.
안녕하세요, 고위관료님.
Thank you sir
감사합니다
I am not going to
나는하지 않을 것이다
do you drive a car?
당신은 차를 운전합니까?
Correct.
옳은.
I'm a car driver
나는 자동차 운전사야
How long have you been coming to the hotel?
호텔에 오신 지 얼마나 되셨나요?
Soon, one month more.
이제 곧 한 달이 더 걸립니다.
What about Mr. Zhou's legs?
저우 씨의 다리는 어떻습니까?
What's that?
그게 뭐야?
I heard last week
지난주에 들었어
Boss Zhou you guys had a car accident.
저우 상사 당신들은 교통사고를 당했습니다.
His leg is broken.
그의 다리가 부러졌습니다.
How is the recovery going?
회복은 어떻게 진행되고 있나요?
It's much better.
훨씬 나아졌습니다.
The food lately has been delicious.
최근 음식이 맛있었어요.
Please convey my regards to him.
그에게 안부 전해주세요.
Good, sir.
좋습니다.
Good.
좋은.
Where are you two going?
둘이 어디 가나요?
Shrimp on the floor is not clean
바닥에 있는 새우가 깨끗하지 않아요
immediately after eating diarrhea.
설사를 먹은 직후.
Pack your things
물건을 싸세요
get out of here quickly
빨리 여기서 나가
go go
가다
everyone go!
다들 가!
How
어떻게
The counterfeit money factory is in warehouse 23.
위조지폐 공장은 23번 창고에 있어요.
Do you have any new discoveries?
새로운 발견이 있나요?
To the left of the workshop entrance
작업실 입구 왼쪽
there is a red button,
빨간 버튼이 있는데,
should have been an alarm.
알람이 울렸어야 했어요.
Factory producing weapons and materials for the Japanese army
일본군용 무기 및 재료를 생산하는 공장
will set an alarm like this.
이렇게 알람을 설정해 드릴게요.
We have to think of a way
우리는 방법을 생각해야 해
so that the warning is not triggered.
경고가 발생하지 않도록 합니다.
Now there is still 1 hour
이제 아직 1시간 남았다
there's still an hour.
아직 한 시간 남았어.
We gather with the Storm Team first.
먼저 폭풍 팀과 모였습니다.
We will create a specific action plan
구체적인 실행 계획을 수립하겠습니다.
according to the latest situation we have.
우리가 가지고 있는 최신 상황에 따르면.
Good.
좋은.
Director Jiang.
장 감독.
I'm Storm Team Leader, Tao Dachun.
폭풍팀 리더 타오다춘 입니다.
Two!
둘!
All members of the Storm Team...
폭풍팀의 모든 구성원들...
Listen to Director Jiang's instructions.
장 감독의 지시를 들어보세요.
Director Jiang, you guys are great.
장 감독님, 정말 훌륭하십니다.
Can sneak into Japanese factories
일본 공장에 몰래 들어갈 수 있다
These are all blessings
이것들은 모두 축복이다
someone helped us get a labor certificate.
누군가 우리가 노동 증명서를 받도록 도와줬어요.
Who is that good?
누가 그렇게 좋은데?
I can't tell you his name.
나는 그의 이름을 말할 수 없습니다.
I can only tell you.
나는 단지 당신에게 말할 수 있습니다.
He is the one we saved
그 사람은 우리가 구한 사람이야
people from the evil department
사악한 부서의 사람들
code, 5 Red Hearts.
코드, 레드 하트 5개.
Understand.
이해하다.
This is Hong Tao Wu.
홍타오우입니다.
Hello, Captain Tao.
안녕하세요, 타오 선장님.
Still a girl
아직 여자야
great, great.
좋아 좋아.
He is the Captain
그는 선장이다
chairman of the Sixth Team of the Su and Zhejiang Action Committee.
소(蘇)절강 행동위원회 제6팀 위원장.
Liu Wuchang.
류우창.
Two.
둘.
This.
이것.
He is...
그는...
I introduce myself
제 소개를하겠습니다
chen Jia Ping
첸 지아 핑
a traitor.
배신자.
Traitor?
배신자?
This problem is long to tell.
이 문제는 말하기가 길다.
But he is now on our side.
하지만 그는 이제 우리 편입니다.
Two.
둘.
Director Jiang.
장 감독.
I want to know right away
바로 알고 싶어요
division of factory buildings uniformly.
공장 건물을 균일하게 분할합니다.
To create a specific action plan.
구체적인 실행 계획을 수립합니다.
Good.
좋은.
Please
제발
have you heard clearly, right?
분명히 들었지?
Already.
이미.
This operation,
이 작전은,
there can be no mistakes in every procedure.
모든 과정에는 실수가 있을 수 없습니다.
This time it's our mission
이번에는 우리의 임무야
can only succeed,
성공할 수 있을 뿐이고,
cannot fail.
실패할 수 없습니다.
Good.
좋은.
The time is almost here.
시간이 거의 다 왔습니다.
Get ready to go
갈 준비를 하세요
Good.
좋은.
You stay here,
당신은 여기있어,
Why?
왜?
Stay cool.
침착.
I won't kill him
나는 그를 죽이지 않을 것이다
after the operation is complete
작업이 완료된 후
I will let it go.
나는 그것을 놓아줄 것이다.
I'm also not interested in participating in your actions.
나는 또한 당신의 행동에 참여하는 데 관심이 없습니다.
Director Jiang?
장 감독?
Can let my wife stay here
내 아내가 여기 머물도록 놔둬도 될까요?
accompany me to chat?
나랑 채팅하러 같이 갈래?
What do you think?
어떻게 생각하나요?
He must join in the action.
그는 그 행동에 동참해야 합니다.
Good.
좋은.
My wife.
내 아내.
Here.
여기.
Then I won't be able to protect you anymore.
그러면 나는 더 이상 당신을 보호할 수 없을 것입니다.
act,
행동,
you have to be careful.
조심해야 해.
Look at it.
보세요.
They did this to me.
그들은 나에게 이런 짓을 했습니다.
Work hard for them.
그들을 위해 열심히 일하십시오.
Totally inappropriate.
완전히 부적절합니다.
Bai Qian.
바이첸.
Until.
까지.
Have you remembered your movement task?
당신의 움직임 과제를 기억했나요?
Already.
이미.
Later, when you act,
나중에 연기를 하게 되면
be careful
조심하세요
far away!
멀리!
Don't come forward.
앞으로 나오지 마세요.
Before 8.15
8.15 이전
Drive the car to the T-junction behind the military clothing factory
군복공장 뒤 T자형 교차로까지 차를 타고 이동하세요.
Remember, you have to turn off the lights.
불을 꺼야 한다는 점을 기억하세요.
Turn from the west.
서쪽에서 돌아라.
Avoiding help that might come.
올지도 모르는 도움을 피합니다.
Which may come.
올 수도 있습니다.
Good.
좋은.
Move.
이동하다.
See you later
나중에 봐요
why not let Chen Jiaping come along?
Chen Jiaping을 따라오면 어떨까요?
Japanese maybe
일본어 어쩌면
already got PKT banknotes
이미 PKT 지폐를 받았어요
and it should be under this counterfeit money factory
그리고 이 위조지폐공장 지하에 있어야지
our mission this time
이번에 우리의 임무
not only destroying counterfeit money factories,
위조지폐 공장을 파괴하는 것뿐만 아니라
also took back the coins
동전도 되찾았어
although Chen Jia Ping has helped us a lot
Chen Jia Ping이 우리에게 많은 도움을 주긴 했지만
but he's not our guy
하지만 그 사람은 우리 사람이 아니야
if he knew the news about the bronze version,...
브론즈 버전 소식을 알았더라면...
Even to the point of leaking information to the Communist Party.
심지어 공산당에 정보를 유출할 정도까지요.
That will have a big impact on our plans.
그것은 우리 계획에 큰 영향을 미칠 것입니다.
Already home.
이미 집에 있습니다.
In front of the door there were 2 Japanese soldiers
문 앞에는 일본군 2명이 서 있었다.
and foreman Sun
그리고 선 감독님
other than the gatekeeper
게이트키퍼 외에
in total there were ten Japanese soldiers.
총 10명의 일본군이 있었습니다.
There were nine who left.
떠난 사람은 9명이었습니다.
There should be one more person
한명이라도 더 있어야 해
Mrs. Agung smokes.
아궁 부인은 담배를 피운다.
Here.
여기.
Did you see the red alarm
빨간색 경보를 보셨나요?
in that room?
그 방에?
Have seen it.
그것을 본 적이 있다.
Get rid of this guy first.
먼저 이 사람부터 없애세요.
Go away.
저리 가요.
Key
열쇠
Mr. Head,
헤드 씨,
This is a fake paper
이건 가짜 종이야
but where did this guy go
그런데 이 사람은 어디로 갔나요?
where is the equipment?
장비는 어디에 있나요?
There is a secret passage here.
여기에는 비밀통로가 있습니다.
You guys stand up first, don't move.
너희들 먼저 일어나, 움직이지 마.
I went down to see what was happening.
나는 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 확인하기 위해 내려갔습니다.
Chief.
셰프.
How
어떻게
the counterfeit money factory must have been transferred.
위조지폐 공장을 이전한 게 틀림없어요.
The bottom part is clogged.
밑부분이 막혀있습니다.
Blocked.
막힌.
Could it possibly explode?
혹시 폭발할 수도 있나요?
The counterfeit money factory must be underground.
위조지폐 공장은 지하에 있어야 합니다.
Otherwise we wouldn't find fake banknotes
그렇지 않으면 가짜 지폐를 찾을 수 없습니다
It is just
그건 그저
Why?
왜?
They suddenly moved.
그들은 갑자기 움직였습니다.
Mr Director,
이사님,
what are your plans now?
지금 당신의 계획은 무엇입니까?
Disband first.
먼저 해체하세요.
Road.
도로.
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
How did you get out?
어떻게 나왔나요?
I'll tell you later.
나중에 말해 줄게.
The Military Police Squadron will arrive soon.
헌병대대가 곧 도착할 예정이다.
We definitely can't get out of the main door.
우리는 확실히 정문에서 나갈 수 없습니다.
So how?
그래서 방법?
Blow up the wall.
벽을 폭파하세요.
Hide.
숨다.
Then ran outside
그러다가 밖으로 뛰쳐나갔어
smash the wall and hide.
벽을 부수고 숨으세요.
Hide.
숨다.
Come with me back.
나와 함께 돌아오세요.
Fast!
빠른!
Hurry up.
서둘러요.
Road!
도로!
Protect Director Jiang.
장 국장을 보호하라.
Split up, see you at the warehouse
헤어지세요 창고에서 만나요
See you at the warehouse
창고에서 만나요
go
가다
Hurry up.
서둘러요.
We go.
우리는 간다.
What does it mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
Even though you saved us
우리를 구해주셨는데도
I am very grateful to you
나는 당신에게 매우 감사합니다
but you know too much.
하지만 당신은 너무 많은 것을 알고 있습니다.
If I want to betray you,
내가 당신을 배신하고 싶다면,
I'll wait until now.
지금까지 기다리겠습니다.
You count
당신은 중요합니다
I really will believe it
정말 믿을게요
are you just a common traitor?
넌 그냥 평범한 배신자야?
You can lie to the left twin,
왼쪽 쌍둥이에게 거짓말을 할 수 있습니다.
but you can't lie to me.
하지만 당신은 나에게 거짓말을 할 수 없습니다.
I really shouldn't have saved you.
정말 당신을 구하지 말았어야 했어요.
Which you shouldn't do too much.
너무 많이 해서는 안 되는 일입니다.
You shouldn't be involved in our operation.
당신은 우리 작전에 개입하면 안 됩니다.
Nor should he marry Zuo Shuang Tao.
또한 그는 Zuo Shuang Tao와 결혼해서는 안됩니다.
However, I don't regret it.
그러나 나는 그것을 후회하지 않습니다.
For the woman I love,
내가 사랑하는 여자를 위해서,
whatever is appropriate.
무엇이든지 적절합니다.
Don't know, Director Jiang.
모르겠어요, 장 감독님.
For the woman you love,
당신이 사랑하는 여자를 위해,
What can Miss Han Lu do?
한루 씨는 무엇을 할 수 있나요?
Wait!
기다리다!
Do not move
이동하지 않습니다
You think we'll believe your bullshit?
우리가 네 헛소리를 믿을 것 같아?
How did Bai Qian die?
백천은 어떻게 죽었나요?
Why would the Japanese know our plans?
왜 일본인들이 우리 계획을 알겠습니까?
If Chen Jiaping really wants to betray us
Chen Jiaping이 정말로 우리를 배신하고 싶다면
why do you still want to help us?
왜 아직도 우리를 돕고 싶어?
He just wants to save you.
그는 단지 당신을 구하고 싶어합니다.
Of course I just want to save my wife
물론 난 단지 내 아내를 구하고 싶을 뿐이야
who wants to help bastards like you?
누가 너 같은 놈을 돕고 싶어?
According to you
당신에 따르면
where is Director Jiang?
장 감독님은 어디 계시나요?
You go ask him?
가서 물어볼까?
Why ask me?
왜 나한테 물어?
Say no?
안된다고?
If you still don't say so
아직도 그렇게 말하지 않는다면
believe it or not I will shoot you dead
믿거나 말거나 널 총으로 쏴 죽일 거야
lower the gun
총을 낮추다
put the gun down.
총을 내려놔.
Let him go.
그분을 석방시켜 주시 ​​오.
Why?
왜?
I believe him
나는 그를 믿는다
Do you believe Chen Jia Ping?
Chen Jia Ping을 믿으십니까?
He is a traitor,
그는 배신자다,
I believe in the Left Twin.
나는 좌파 쌍둥이를 믿습니다.
So I also trust the people he trusts
그래서 나는 또한 그가 신뢰하는 사람들을 믿습니다.
take Chen Jia Ping away
Chen Jia Ping을 데려가세요
treat him well
그 사람을 잘 대해줘
don't interfere in our affairs anymore.
더 이상 우리 일에 간섭하지 마세요.
Stay cool.
침착.
There won't be a next time.
다음에는 없을 것입니다.
Do you know why
왜인지 아세요?
won't let you join the final act?
마지막 막에 합류하게 놔두지 않을 건가요?
Why
왜
because of the CCP copper coins
CCP 구리 동전 때문에
very likely fell into the hands of the Japanese.
아마도 일본군의 손에 넘어갔을 것이다.
At first he thought he could find it
처음에 그는 그것을 찾을 수 있을 것이라고 생각했습니다
in a counterfeit money factory,
위조지폐공장에서
however, he doesn't want you to know.
그러나 그는 당신이 알기를 원하지 않습니다.
According to you,
당신에 따르면,
Where has the counterfeit money factory been transferred to?
위폐공장은 어디로 이전됐나요?
Now I also have no clue anymore.
이제 나 역시 더 이상 아무 것도 모른다.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Who are you really?
당신은 정말로 누구입니까?
What? Who am I?
무엇? 나는 누구입니까?
Karena Jiang Zhaoguo
카레나 지앙 자오궈
have the same suspicions as me,
저와 같은 의심을 가지고 계시네요.
just wanted to kill you.
그냥 당신을 죽이고 싶었어요.
Is...
이다...
Are you from over there?
당신은 거기 출신입니까?
What's over here?
여기에 무엇이 있습니까?
Me
나
is your husband.
당신 남편이에요.
You just need to remember this.
이것만 기억하시면 됩니다.
I'm guessing you won't talk much either.
내 생각엔 당신도 별로 말을 하지 않을 것 같아요.
It's just that one day I was afraid.
다만 어느 날은 두려웠을 뿐입니다.
You're not even my husband
당신은 내 남편도 아니잖아
other?
다른?
I dare not guarantee
감히 보장할 수가 없어요
but only this thing
하지만 이것뿐이야
I really promise
정말 약속해요
Tuan Jiang.
투안 지앙.
Here are the ice cubes and whiskey I prepared for you.
여기 제가 준비한 얼음과 위스키가 있습니다.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Mr. Jiang is really great
장 씨는 정말 대단해요
he can find the location of our underground factory
그는 우리 지하 공장의 위치를 ​​알아낼 수 있어요
I saw a great one
나는 훌륭한 것을 보았다
it should be you
너여야만 해
Dahua hotel, my whereabouts were exposed.
다화호텔, 내 행방이 노출됐다.
Today,
오늘,
I've planned this all
이 모든 건 내가 계획했어
in the end it was in vain.
결국 그것은 헛된 일이었습니다.
I like to talk openly
나는 공개적으로 이야기하는 것을 좋아한다
talk openly like this.
이렇게 대놓고 얘기하세요.
Mr. Jiang can stay here temporarily.
장 씨는 여기에 일시적으로 머물 수 있습니다.
Your daily needs
귀하의 일상적인 요구 사항
we will prepare it for you.
우리는 당신을 위해 그것을 준비할 것입니다.
Oh yes
바로 이거 야
In the room I have prepared a jacket for you.
방에 재킷을 준비했어요.
No need for a suit.
양복은 필요 없습니다.
This one...
이 하나...
Quite good.
꽤 좋은.
One.
하나.
I can drink.
나는 마실 수 있다.
But that doesn't mean that after drinking your wine,
하지만 그렇다고 해서 와인을 마신 후에는
I will discuss cooperation with you.
나는 당신과 협력을 논의할 것입니다.
Future problems,
미래의 문제,
we can talk slowly.
우리 천천히 얘기하면 돼.
However,
하지만,
I want to ask Mr. Jiang something.
장 씨에게 물어보고 싶은 게 있어요.
Say it.
말해.
Where did this labor certificate come from?
이 노동 증명서는 어디에서 왔습니까?
Faked?
속이는?
We've checked.
우리는 확인했습니다.
The labor certificate is genuine.
노동증명서는 진짜입니다.
In each acquaintance letter there must be a different number.
각 지인 편지에는 다른 번호가 있어야 합니다.
If you look at this number,
이 숫자를 보면,
we found
우리는 발견
that this labor certificate
이 노동 증명서
comes from Taihe commercial bank.
태허상업은행에서 왔습니다.
In Chongqing there are also our people.
충칭에도 우리 인민이 있습니다.
We recently received information,
최근에 정보를 얻었는데,
there was a military member named Hong Tao 5,
홍도5라는 군인이 있었는데,
lurking inside Taihe Company.
태화회사 내부에 숨어있습니다.
This labor certificate
이 노동증명서
is a gift from Hong Tao Wu, right?
홍타오우가 준 선물 맞죠?
I don't know Taihe Company.
저는 태화회사를 모릅니다.
Tuan Jiang,
투안 지앙,
At least we have respected you.
적어도 우리는 당신을 존경했습니다.
I hope you will also give me an honor.
당신도 나에게 영광을 주시기를 바랍니다.
Cooperation or not,
협력이 있든 없든,
we can talk about it later.
나중에 얘기하자.
But this thing
하지만 이건
You have to give an account to me.
당신은 나에게 계정을 제공해야합니다.
If not,
그렇지 않다면,
everyone will feel embarrassed.
다들 당황스러울 겁니다.
The counterfeit money factory has been transferred,
위조지폐공장을 이전하였고,
nothing worked.
아무것도 작동하지 않았습니다.
We lost a lot of teams.
우리는 많은 팀을 잃었습니다.
I might be involved too.
나도 참여할 수도 있다.
Besides that,
그 외에도
The Zuo twins are already doubting my identity.
Zuo 쌍둥이는 이미 내 정체성을 의심하고 있습니다.
Wang Dapu, this person.
왕다푸, 이 사람.
Financial expert, copper engraver.
금융 전문가, 구리 조각사.
Has participated in minting and issuing coins.
코인 주조 및 발행에 참여했습니다.
True identity
진정한 정체성
is a military spy with a wild goose code.
기러기 코드를 사용하는 군사 스파이입니다.
After stealing copper coins,
구리 동전을 훔친 후,
fled to Shanghai.
상하이로 도망쳤다.
There is information that this person was captured by the Japanese.
이 사람이 일본인에게 포로로 잡혔다는 정보가 있습니다.
If there is new information, contact the organization.
새로운 정보가 있으면 해당 기관에 문의하세요.
Everything,
모든 것,
today we invite a special expert
오늘 우리는 특별한 전문가를 초대합니다
to give a lecture to you
당신에게 강의를 하려고
welcome
환영
good greetings to classmates
반 친구들에게 좋은 인사